Urvashi Sharma

Address U-9/6,7,8 U-block, DLF Phase 3, Gurugram Phone 9971362788 Urvashi.sharma.hr@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Looking forward to scope of enhancing my personal skills and gaining maximum knowledge during my tenure to contribute to the growth of the firm I am a part of. I possess 2+ years of experience in Human Resource role handling Talent Acquisition and HR operations.

Employment Details

Sep. 2019- till date

fPEE SAFE (Radcliffe Hygiene Pvt. Ltd.) Gurgaon

Sr. Talent Acquisition

- Reviewing resumes and applications, conducting recruitment interviews and providing the necessary inputs during the hiring process.
- Conducting first round of telephonic interview for the candidates to schedule interviews.
- Conducting employee orientation and facilitating newcomers joining formalities.
- Recording, maintaining and monitoring attendance to ensure employee punctuality.
- Maintaining and regularly updating master database (personal file, personal database, etc.) of each employee.
- Resolving grievances or queries that any of the employees have.
- Preparing letters such as offer or confirmation and appointment letter.
- Training new or existing employees.
- Maintaining HR records, such as those related to compensation, health and medical insurance.
- Communicating and explaining the organization's HR policies to the employees.
- Maintaining intern's data, offer letter & NDA, stipend etc.
- Maintaining freelancers/ Retainer's database, issuing them agreement and NDA and payments.

June 2018-July 2019

Sky Ways Proptech Associate Pvt. Ltd. Noida

HR Manager (Training & Commercial Leasing)

- Directed all human resources functions including recruitment, hiring, training and employee relations.
- Oversaw employee relations, benefits & compensation, staffing, management development and work force analysis.
- Consistently maintained the highest level of confidentiality.
- Work with the marketing and sales team to devise and implement new strategies for the assigned area
- Prepare lease agreements, revenue collection reports, and other files as required.
- Coordinated with the marketing department and developed strategies to approach target groups through different mediums.
- Met with corporate clients and finalized terms and conditions for various lease agreements.
- Performed all other activities assigned during the course of my job.

May- 2017 to july-2017 **BIG BAZAAR (FUTURE GROUP)**

HR Intern.

- Human resource assistant collaborated with team of HR professionals, providing administrative support including filing, and posting throughout the retail
- Assisting and coordinating in daily HR activities, including interacting with managers of other departments
- Collecting, scanning, and sorting job applications for candidate and calling deserving candidates for interviews
- Helping in preparing identify cards, log id and passwords of new hires.
- Maintained and updated employee files and company documentation.

Education

IMED, Bharati Vidyapeeth Deemed University, PUNE.

Master's in Business Administration with specialization in Human Resource Management

St. Methodist College, HNGBU. Roorkee.

Graduation in Bachelor's in Commerce

Saraswati Vidya Mandir, Roorkee

Intermediate (Commerce) 70%, CBSE

Saraswati Vidya Mandir, Roorkee

High School 76%, CBSE.

Additional Skills

- **HR Policy Execution**
- Good communication skills
- **General Administration**
- Organizational Development
- Personnel records maintenance
- **Best Practice**

2016-2018

2011-2014

2011

2009